<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ruby on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/ruby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ruby on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/ruby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pointers vs References</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/go-pointers-vs-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/go-pointers-vs-references/</guid>
      <description>Some languages including C, C++ support pointers. Other languages including C++, Java, Python, Ruby, Perl and PHP all support references. On the surface both references and pointers are very similar, both are used to have one variable provide access to another. With both providing a lot of the same capabilities, it’s often unclear what is different between these different mechanisms. In this article I will illustrate the difference between pointers and references.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 MongoDB 2.6 Drivers Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/mongodb2-6-drivers-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/mongodb2-6-drivers-released/</guid>
      <description>I’m pleased to announce the coordinated release of drivers in 9 languages in preparation for the release of MongoDB 2.6. This is the largest driver release in the history of MongoDB, both in terms of code changes as well as in terms of drivers released. Official Drivers for C, C++, C# (.net), Java, Node.js, PHP, Python, Ruby and Scala were all released with Perl following shortly. In the upcoming weeks community drivers will be updated to take advantage of the new features present in MongoDB 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build your first MongoDB App in Ruby @ StrangeLoop 2013</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-your-first-mongodb-app-in-ruby-strangeloop-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-your-first-mongodb-app-in-ruby-strangeloop-2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An updated version of the &lt;a href=&#34;presentation/building-your-first-mongodb-app-oscon-2012/&#34;&gt;very popular workshop I gave at OSCON last year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This presentation was given at Strangeloop 2013 as a 3 hour interactive workshop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Modern Web Applications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-modern-web-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-modern-web-applications/</guid>
      <description>I gave this presentation to a packed house at DevCon5 in NYC July 24th. DevCon5 is a web developers conference and this year it focused on HTML5. This was one of the hardest presentations I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on for the simple fact that the audience had name recognition, but not familiarity with the database industry. Typically I&amp;rsquo;ve leaned on the fact that most participants were familiar with at least one database prior to my presentation, I had no such luxury here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving the most viewed presentation on slideshare ever at OSCON</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-gave-the-most-viewed-presentation-in-the-history-of-oscon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-gave-the-most-viewed-presentation-in-the-history-of-oscon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/oscon_spf13.jpg&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Steve Francia at OSCON&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  At OSCON 2012 in Portland I gave a presentation on building your first MongoDB application. Over 150 people were in the audience, a pretty significant number of this type of hands on tutorial. Certainly worth the weeks of preparation that went into developing it. While at OSCON I put the slides online at SlideShare where during the four day conference the amassed over 20k views and within a couple weeks over 30k views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building your first MongoDB app - OSCON 2012</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-your-first-mongodb-app-oscon-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/building-your-first-mongodb-app-oscon-2012/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/MongoDB-at-oscon-2012.png&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  This is a 3 hour tutorial I wrote for and gave at OSCON 2012.
Here is the summary:
This tutorial will introduce the features of MongoDB by building a simple location-based application using MongoDB. The tutorial will cover the basics of MongoDB’s document model, query language, map-reduce framework and deployment architecture.
The tutorial will be divided into 5 sections:
 Data modeling with MongoDB: documents, collections and databases Querying your data: simple queries, geospatial queries, and text-searching Writes and updates: using MongoDB’s atomic update modifiers Trending and analytics: Using mapreduce and MongoDB’s aggregation framework Deploying the sample application  Besides the knowledge to start building their own applications with MongoDB, attendees will finish the session with a working application they use to check into locations around Portland from any HTML5 enabled phone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spf13-vim : Steve Francia&#39;s Vim Distribution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/project/spf13-vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/project/spf13-vim/</guid>
      <description>spf13-vim is a distribution of vim plugins and resources for Vim, Gvim and MacVim.
It is a good starting point for anyone intending to use VIM for development running equally well on Windows, Linux, *nix and Mac.
The distribution is completely customisable using a ~/.vimrc.local and ~/.vimrc.bundles.local Vim RC files.
Unlike traditional VIM plugin structure, which similar to UNIX throws all files into common directories, making updating or disabling plugins a real mess, spf13-vim 3 uses the Vundle plugin management system to have a well organized vim directory (Similar to mac&amp;rsquo;s app folders).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Web Sites (LAMP) : Top Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/scaling-web-sites-lamp-top-resources-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/scaling-web-sites-lamp-top-resources-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/failwhale.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Image via Wikipedia&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Image via Wikipedia &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Luckily it’s 2009 and there have been a bunch of successful websites that have had to deal with large scalability challenges. Many have been kind enough to share their knowledge with the world. Here is a list of the best books, articles, presentations and practices from the likes of Twitter, Facebook, Flickr and more.
Books Building Scalable Web Sites Building, scaling, and optimizing the next generation of web applications by Cal Henderson</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>