<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://jlab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jlab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Should a Modern Practical Programming Language Look Like</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/presentation/what-should-a-modern-practical-programming-language-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/presentation/what-should-a-modern-practical-programming-language-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Keynote delivered at &lt;a href=&#34;https://landingfestival.com/&#34;&gt;The Landing Festival – Berlin&lt;/a&gt;. This presentation describes the many inspirations and influences of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://golang.org&#34;&gt;Go programming language&lt;/a&gt; and goes into detail about how we shaped and created the language.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo: A fast and flexible static site generator built in GoLang</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/project/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/project/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/hugo.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Hugo Website&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Hugo Website &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Hugo is a static site generator written in Go. It is optimized for speed, easy use and configurability. Hugo takes a directory with content and templates and renders them into a full html website.
Hugo makes use of markdown files with front matter for meta data.
Written in GoLang for speed, Hugo is significantly faster than most other static site generators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Projects Fail</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-projects-fail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-projects-fail/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/What_Happens_When_Brakes_Fail.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;train crash&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Regardless of your title or degree of experience, any misstep could result in a failed project. It’s a good habit to review the following two slide shows, if nothing else to provide a good confirmation that you are on the right track.
Why Projects Fail: Obstacles and SolutionsView more documents from Michael Krigsman.
Rome Death March Nov2009 View more documents from yourdon.
Related articles  Why Software Projects Fail (ribomation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are you still shopping offline?</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-are-you-still-shopping-offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-are-you-still-shopping-offline/</guid>
      <description>Today I visited one of the largest national office supply outlets. I had a specific purpose in mind. I needed to pickup 2 wireless routers and 1 audio cable. What transpired caused me to wonder why anyone does any offline shopping anymore.
My experience at the store caused me to reflect on the many things we simply put up with at the store which we would never permit online.
To begin with I had to drive to the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SVK to Increase Productivity</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/using-svk-to-increase-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/using-svk-to-increase-productivity/</guid>
      <description>SVK is a client for SVN built using perl. It makes a number of improvements over the standard svn client, while retaining much of the same feel. It works with the standard Subversion server and works perfectly in an environment with some users using svn and some using svk on the client side. It provides a number of sizable advantages over the standard svn client and is a must have for any development project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are you not on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-are-you-not-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/why-are-you-not-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/Twitter_Badge_1.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Image via Wikipedia&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Image via Wikipedia &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Over the last 2 weeks I have found myself asking that question more times than I can remember. When I first heard about microblogging—or Twitter, the primary service that started the microblogging movement—over a year ago I thought it was a stupid fad and wouldn’t last. I mean what value can possibly be passed along in 140 characters or less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-25_jlab_blog1582624561/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-25_jlab_blog1582624561/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github提供免费3员工私有代码库 Free private Github repository license 3 employees Open</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-27_jlab_blog1582789748/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-27_jlab_blog1582789748/</guid>
      <description>Github提供免费3员工私有代码库 Free private Github repository license 3 employees Open  As title said, it is convenience to StartUps, and bundled youe company to Github It is a promotion bait for programmer~! Enjoy it! Source text If you’re a GitHub user, but you don’t pay, this is a good week. Historically, GitHub  always offered free accounts but the caveat was that your code had to be public. To get private repositories, you had to pay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test 6 again</title>
      <link>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-27_jlab_blog1582779726/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jlab.github.io/post/2020-02-27_jlab_blog1582779726/</guid>
      <description>test 6 again  say something here  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>