<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenSky on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/OpenSky/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OpenSky on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/OpenSky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blending Mongo and RDBMS for ecommerce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/blending-mongo-and-rdbms-for-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/blending-mongo-and-rdbms-for-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Justin Hileman and I presented at MongoNYC 2011 to a packed house. Our presentation outlines both why someone would want to use MongoDB for ecommerce and how we overcame some of it’s limitations by incorporating mysql into our infrastructure.
 &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/l6zwy.jpg&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Presenting at MongoNYC 2011&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Blending MongoDB and RDBMS for ecommerce
View more presentations from Steve Francia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB &amp; Ecommerce : A Perfect Combination</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-ecommerce-a-perfect-combination/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-ecommerce-a-perfect-combination/</guid>
      <description>Last night I gave a presentation on MongoDB &amp;amp; Ecommerce. OpenSky is the first company to use MongoDB in production for ecommerce. I shared why we went this route, and why it’s an obvious and powerful combination. At OpenSky we use MongoDB to develop the next ecommerce platform. OpenSky also uses Symfony 2, Doctrine 2, PHP 5.3, PHPUnit 3.5, jQuery, node.js, Git (with gitflow) and a touch of Java and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling on OpenSky</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/selling-on-opensky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/selling-on-opensky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/opensky_new-logo.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;OpenSky&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  As anyone who reads my blog or follows my tweets knows, I’ve been working for a new startup called OpenSky since February 2010. We’ve launched a new ecommerce platform and aim to reinvent ecommerce as people know it online.
One of the big things we are doing is making it so anyone can sell OpenSky products from anywhere online. In the spirit of eating my own dogfood, I’ve become an OpenSky seller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/transitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/transitions/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/opensky-logo.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;OpenSky Logo&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  I couldn’t be more excited to announce that I have accepted a position at The Open Sky Project. I am leading the architecture, development and technology.
It’s rare in life that one has the opportunity to do what they love to do and be paid to do it. Even rarer is to do something great with people you love working with. At OpenSky I have found this and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>