<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/Linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 10:43:50 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/Linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>the future of the Operating System - LinuxCon 2015 keynote</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/the-future-of-the-os-linuxcon-2015-keynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 10:43:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/the-future-of-the-os-linuxcon-2015-keynote/</guid>
      <description>Given as a keynote at LinuxCon + CloudOpen Japan 2015.
Linux has become the foundation for infrastructure everywhere as it defined application portability from the desktop to the phone and from to the data center to the cloud. As applications become increasingly distributed in nature, the Docker platform serves as the cornerstone of Linux’s evolution solidifying the dominance of Linux today and into tomorrow.
Transcript  The Future of the Operating System What is an Operating System ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Browser as an application platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/the-browser-as-a-application-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/the-browser-as-a-application-platform/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/Chromium_Logo.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;chromium logo&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  With Google launching their chrome book is significant as it reflects a substantial shift in the world of computing. For the first time ever, the application platform isn’t the operating system, nor is it adobe air, .net or java, it’s the browser. The browser once, a simple tool for fetching and rendering content is now the most important application platform in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unix Jobs Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/unix-jobs-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/unix-jobs-management/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/300px-GNU_Screen.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;GNU Screen&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Every self respecting linux, mac os X or *nix user should have a solid handle on managing jobs in unix. The following will explain how to run tasks in the background, bring tasks to the foreground, background already running tasks and keeping a task running while logged out.
Run a task in the background All you need to to is follow a command with the ‘&amp;amp;’ character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human readable du sorted by size</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/human-readable-du-sorted-by-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/human-readable-du-sorted-by-size/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/du.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;example output of du UNIX command&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  du is the *nix command for disk usage. It tells you how much space everything in the given directory is taking up. GNU du introduced a handy option -h making it human readable, or showing sizes using K, M, G rather than bytes. Unfortunately this makes it not sortable numerically. Here’s how to sort du by size and keep it as human readable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Web Sites (LAMP) : Top Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/scaling-web-sites-lamp-top-resources-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/scaling-web-sites-lamp-top-resources-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/failwhale.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Image via Wikipedia&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Image via Wikipedia &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Luckily it’s 2009 and there have been a bunch of successful websites that have had to deal with large scalability challenges. Many have been kind enough to share their knowledge with the world. Here is a list of the best books, articles, presentations and practices from the likes of Twitter, Facebook, Flickr and more.
Books Building Scalable Web Sites Building, scaling, and optimizing the next generation of web applications by Cal Henderson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup Your Files</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/backup-your-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/backup-your-files/</guid>
      <description>One of the worst experiences you can have as a computer operator is to realize you (or something else) just did something and wiped out your files. The purpose of this article is to show you how to automatically backup your files often and automatically. I use this setup to backup my documents every hour (I save more often then that). This gives me hourly versions of all my files I am working on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>