<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>career on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in career on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Rands Posts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/my-favorite-rands-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/my-favorite-rands-posts/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/rands.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;rands in repose&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  If you don’t know Rands (real name Michael Lopp), you should. His blog is full of excellent content from someone who successfully figured out how to transition from managing bits to Managing Humans (also the title of his first book). Whether you are a developer, a tech manager, or manage something else, you’ll find value in his posts. I’ve been reading his blog for years and it’s influenced my decisions greatly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch what you say</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/watch-what-you-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/watch-what-you-say/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/shhh.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;shh..&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; shh.. &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/81619620@N00/3297040703&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Gustty &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  I came across an article today titled “Help! My boss is on twitter“. Allow me to share a secret with you, if you current boss isn’t on twitter yet, I can guarantee that your next one will be. Social media has caught on like wildfire. In all the excitement too often people forget that everything that you say on twitter / facebook and others is being published and recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Right People</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/finding-the-right-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/finding-the-right-people/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/twitter-following.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;people&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Since I began at Open Sky a few weeks ago I have been tasked with building out a great team. Over the course of my career I have interviewed hundreds of people (mostly developers) and hired dozens. At OpenSky I was able to find and hire 6 fantastic employees in my first 6 weeks and wanted to share some of the tips and techniques I have learned over the years and found successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/transitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/transitions/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/opensky-logo.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;OpenSky Logo&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  I couldn’t be more excited to announce that I have accepted a position at The Open Sky Project. I am leading the architecture, development and technology.
It’s rare in life that one has the opportunity to do what they love to do and be paid to do it. Even rarer is to do something great with people you love working with. At OpenSky I have found this and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>