<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nosql on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/nosql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nosql on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/nosql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Hadoop: NoSQL in the Enterprise at Strata NYC 2012</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/big-data-for-the-rest-of-us-at-nyc-strata-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/big-data-for-the-rest-of-us-at-nyc-strata-2012/</guid>
      <description>At the NYC Strata &amp;amp; Hadoop World conference I presented on ‘Not Just Hadoop: NoSQL in the Enterprise’. Robert Lancaster from Orbitz joined me on stage for the final presentation of the Bridge to Big Data track. Mark Madsen did a great job moderating the session and kept the energy high the entire day. Robert shared how Orbitz uses MongoDB with Apache Hadoop to provide real time rates. This is my second time presenting at Strata’s Big Data conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving the most viewed presentation on slideshare ever at OSCON</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-gave-the-most-viewed-presentation-in-the-history-of-oscon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-gave-the-most-viewed-presentation-in-the-history-of-oscon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/oscon_spf13.jpg&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Steve Francia at OSCON&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  At OSCON 2012 in Portland I gave a presentation on building your first MongoDB application. Over 150 people were in the audience, a pretty significant number of this type of hands on tutorial. Certainly worth the weeks of preparation that went into developing it. While at OSCON I put the slides online at SlideShare where during the four day conference the amassed over 20k views and within a couple weeks over 30k views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replication, Durability, and Disaster Recovery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/replication-durability-and-disaster-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/replication-durability-and-disaster-recovery/</guid>
      <description>This session introduces the basic components of high availability before going into a deep dive on MongoDB replication. We’ll explore some of the advanced capabilities with MongoDB replication and best practices to ensure data durability and redundancy. We’ll also look at various deployment scenarios and disaster recovery configurations.
Replication, Durability, and Disaster Recovery
View more presentations from Steve Francia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with MongoDB and PHP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/getting-started-with-mongodb-and-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/getting-started-with-mongodb-and-php/</guid>
      <description>Nearly 3 years ago I discovered a new database that literally changed my life. I know, that’s a pretty bold claim, but it’s true. While leading the engineering team at OpenSky I faced a problem I was well familiar with. How to build a e-commerce product that: 1. Provided performance and scale 2. Handled many verticals and 3. Provided proper indexing on key attributes. In search for a better solution to this problem I encountered MongoDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NoSQL databases and Managing Big Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/nosql-databases-and-managing-big-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/nosql-databases-and-managing-big-data/</guid>
      <description>I had the unique opportunity to present at the annual technology forum Insight Venture Partners holds for their portfolio companies. Over 100 CTOs gathered in NYC to hear from great presenters from companies like 10gen, Tumblr, Shutterstock and Buddy Media.
I’ve included a slightly longer version of the presentation given which includes a few slides that I cut out for brevity to fit in the allocated time while still allowing time for questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Drupal and MongoDB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/getting-started-with-drupal-and-mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/getting-started-with-drupal-and-mongodb/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/Drupal-Admin.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Drupal&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  MongoDB is the most full featured scalable database taking the tech world by storm. Drupal is the standard in content management powering magazines, blogs online newspapers and much more. It’s only natural that they would get together to provide a fast dynamic scalable CMS system. Whenever a Drupal site needs to scale dynamic content they turn to MongoDB to be able to deliver. The Examiner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LDS SORT Tech Conference 2011</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/lds-sort-tech-conference-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/lds-sort-tech-conference-2011/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/sort-win.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;sort conference&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Last week I had the opportunity to attend the LDS Church’s SORT tech conference. Nearly 1200 people were in attendance. There were 23 concurrent tracks and I was able to present two presentations and be on a panel with other NoSQL solutions including Cassandra, CouchDB, Neo4j, Riak and MarkLogic. The panel went for 90 minutes the first half being an 5 – 10 minute introduction of each technology and the second half being a QA period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where have all the good databases gone?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/where-have-all-the-good-databases-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/where-have-all-the-good-databases-gone/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/mongodb-sq.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;mongodb&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Perhaps you’ll recognize these words, “About five years ago I started to notice an odd thing. The products that the database vendors were building had less and less to do with what the customers wanted. … So, what is this growing disconnect?” Those words were written in 2004 by Adam Bosworth, a veteren of Microsoft, Google and BEA. In the 7 years since things have only gotten worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blending Mongo and RDBMS for ecommerce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/blending-mongo-and-rdbms-for-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/blending-mongo-and-rdbms-for-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Justin Hileman and I presented at MongoNYC 2011 to a packed house. Our presentation outlines both why someone would want to use MongoDB for ecommerce and how we overcame some of it’s limitations by incorporating mysql into our infrastructure.
 &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/l6zwy.jpg&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Presenting at MongoNYC 2011&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Blending MongoDB and RDBMS for ecommerce
View more presentations from Steve Francia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Hammer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/the-golden-hammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/the-golden-hammer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/hammer.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;hammer&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/87793853@N00/1430449350&amp;quot;&amp;gt; kyle may &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Every so often a “new” technology catches on. Right now it’s nosql databases. A couple years ago it was Ruby, before that it was java. Each arise because they propose a solution to an existing problem, or in other words a better way of doing something.. something, but not everything.
Unfortunately knowing when to use the technology requires actual experience with it, which never seems to catch up to the hype engine quickly enough, so consequently the technology transforms into a “golden hammer”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NoSQL Databases</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/nosql-databases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/nosql-databases/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/noSQL_people.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;nosql people&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/40888529@N00/4036996146&amp;quot;&amp;gt; langalex &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Amazon, Digg, Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter all started on sql databases (all but Amazon on MySQL) and have transitioned to incorporated nosql databases into their infrastructure, though many utilize both relational databases as well as non-relational ones.
I’ve compiled a few resources to help bring you up to speed on nosql databases.
Major sites using NoSQL  Amazon : (Dynamo) http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>