<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/Programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/Programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating your own Symfony2 Bundle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/creating-your-own-symfony2-bundle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/creating-your-own-symfony2-bundle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/symfony_ss.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;symfony&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Symfony2 is a great web framework. OpenSky is built on this framework and we are one of the largest contributors to it. The primary building block for Symfony2 is a bundle. Through it’s bundle system Symfony 2.0 achieves a level of modularity I haven’t seen in other web frameworks. A bundle permits a developer to add functionality to the framework and is the best way to develop applications with Symfony2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My take on open source licenses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/my-take-on-open-source-licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/my-take-on-open-source-licenses/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/opensource.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;open source&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Open Source licensing can be a confusing and daunting task. Most developers simply adopt licenses of other popular projects. I wanted to shed some light on the most popular licenses and provide some guidance on which one should be used and when.
Disclaimer: I’m not a lawyer, I am not qualified to nor am I imparting sound legal advice.
BSD &amp;amp; MIT Both licenses are very similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIM Crash Course</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/vim-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/vim-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/vim_logo.png&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Most developers know the basics of VIM, enough to edit a conf file, but most stay there, unaware of the power and beauty of vim. One of my developers has expressed desire to abandon the bloated GUI ways of eclipse and discover VIM. I have been using VIM for such a long time I forgot how difficult that transition is. Here are some resources and approaches to help you learn vim.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>