<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pointers vs References</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/go-pointers-vs-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/go-pointers-vs-references/</guid>
      <description>Some languages including C, C++ support pointers. Other languages including C++, Java, Python, Ruby, Perl and PHP all support references. On the surface both references and pointers are very similar, both are used to have one variable provide access to another. With both providing a lot of the same capabilities, it’s often unclear what is different between these different mechanisms. In this article I will illustrate the difference between pointers and references.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 MongoDB 2.6 Drivers Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/mongodb2-6-drivers-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/mongodb2-6-drivers-released/</guid>
      <description>I’m pleased to announce the coordinated release of drivers in 9 languages in preparation for the release of MongoDB 2.6. This is the largest driver release in the history of MongoDB, both in terms of code changes as well as in terms of drivers released. Official Drivers for C, C++, C# (.net), Java, Node.js, PHP, Python, Ruby and Scala were all released with Perl following shortly. In the upcoming weeks community drivers will be updated to take advantage of the new features present in MongoDB 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spf13-vim : Steve Francia&#39;s Vim Distribution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/project/spf13-vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/project/spf13-vim/</guid>
      <description>spf13-vim is a distribution of vim plugins and resources for Vim, Gvim and MacVim.
It is a good starting point for anyone intending to use VIM for development running equally well on Windows, Linux, *nix and Mac.
The distribution is completely customisable using a ~/.vimrc.local and ~/.vimrc.bundles.local Vim RC files.
Unlike traditional VIM plugin structure, which similar to UNIX throws all files into common directories, making updating or disabling plugins a real mess, spf13-vim 3 uses the Vundle plugin management system to have a well organized vim directory (Similar to mac&amp;rsquo;s app folders).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>