<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Editors on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/Editors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Editors on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/Editors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The perfect .vimrc vim config file</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/perfect-vimrc-vim-config-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/perfect-vimrc-vim-config-file/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/vim_logo.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;vim&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  I have spent the last few years tweaking and refining my VIM configuration. This is the ultimate VIM configuration .vimrc file. It is well organized and documented. It is on GitHub so you can always grab the latest. It works well alone, but is intended to be paired with the plugins and configuration found in my complete .vim configuration also hosted on GitHub.
The Perfect .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Vim Config</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/ultimate-vim-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/ultimate-vim-config/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/vim_logo.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;vim&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  I have spent the last few years tweaking and refining my VIM configuration until I had the Ultimate Vim Config. It is well organized and documented taking full advantage of Tpope’s pathogen for a excellent clean and modular configuration. The Ultimate vim config contains the perfect .vimrc file combined with an excellent set of plugins all easily managed thanks to pathogen and git. It is on GitHub so you can always grab the latest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIM Crash Course</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/vim-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/vim-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/vim_logo.png&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Most developers know the basics of VIM, enough to edit a conf file, but most stay there, unaware of the power and beauty of vim. One of my developers has expressed desire to abandon the bloated GUI ways of eclipse and discover VIM. I have been using VIM for such a long time I forgot how difficult that transition is. Here are some resources and approaches to help you learn vim.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>