<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ecommerce on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/ecommerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ecommerce on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/ecommerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB, E-Commerce and Transactions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-e-commerce-and-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-e-commerce-and-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Last week I had the pleasure of attending MongoUK in London. I had a great time presenting and meeting new friends. I even survived two whiteboard sessions where people were invited to ask any question, any at all, about MongoDB.
I gave a pretty significatly revised presentation on MongoDB and E-Commerce with emphasis on transactions. If you saw the presentation at MongoNYC this summer, it’s worth a revisit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting RDBMS with NoSQL for e-commerce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/augmenting-rdbms-with-nosql-for-e-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/augmenting-rdbms-with-nosql-for-e-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/postgresconNYC_ss.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;postgres con&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Justin Hileman and I gave a presentation on “Augmenting RDBMS with NoSQL for e-commerce” at the PgEast 2011 conference. This presentation is really the sequel (no pun intended) to my presentation, MongoDB &amp;amp; Ecommerce : A Perfect Combination. This presentation takes you through how we created a hybrid solution blending both sql and nosql to achieve an optimal solution.
Augmenting RDBMS with MongoDB for ecommerce</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB &amp; Ecommerce : A Perfect Combination</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-ecommerce-a-perfect-combination/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/presentation/mongodb-ecommerce-a-perfect-combination/</guid>
      <description>Last night I gave a presentation on MongoDB &amp;amp; Ecommerce. OpenSky is the first company to use MongoDB in production for ecommerce. I shared why we went this route, and why it’s an obvious and powerful combination. At OpenSky we use MongoDB to develop the next ecommerce platform. OpenSky also uses Symfony 2, Doctrine 2, PHP 5.3, PHPUnit 3.5, jQuery, node.js, Git (with gitflow) and a touch of Java and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing and Improving Conversion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/analyzing-and-improving-conversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/analyzing-and-improving-conversion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Image by LollyKnit via Flickr &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Conversion is one of those core metrics that every business depends on and strives to improve. Improving your conversion rate (while maintaining a consistent traffic level) is the single most important goal any business should have. Not only will your sales increase without adding additional load but your marketing will be more efficient so you can spend more money driving more sales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>