<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Go Hugo blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/go-go-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/go-go-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/spf13-responsive.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;spf13 responsive website&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After after a few months of work I&amp;rsquo;m happy to display the newest incarnation of spf13.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Intellectual Property on Your Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/protect-intellectual-property-on-your-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/protect-intellectual-property-on-your-blog/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/3084905055_694483b898_b.jpeg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;security&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  The protection of your intellectual property, or any information that you post to your blog, forum or website, can be a tricky subject. While there are those unscrupulous few out there in the cyber world who will purposely copy your words as their own, there are more people that are simply ignorant of the laws, unaware that they are stealing when they copy and reuse your musings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Code Viewer 2 for WordPress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/project/github-code-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/project/github-code-viewer/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Code Viewer 2 automatically pulls a file from github and places into any post using a shortcode [github_cv url=&#39;$url&amp;rsquo;] Caches locally (in db), so there isn&amp;rsquo;t a performance hit. Heavily Modified from original plugin by Matt Curry http://www.pseudocoder.com
Installation  Upload GitHub_Code_Viewer.php to the /wp-content/plugins/ directory Activate the plugin through the &amp;lsquo;Plugins&amp;rsquo; menu in WordPress Use the shortcode [github_cv url=&#39;&amp;rsquo;] in your post.  Changelog 2.0  Rewrote as a static class as only one instance is needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion of the Blog-a-thon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/conclusion-of-the-blog-a-thon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/conclusion-of-the-blog-a-thon/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the last post of my blog-a-thon. It has been a learning and growing experience. I have blogged more time in the past 4 weeks as I did the prior 52. It was challenging and rewarding.
I feel I have developed as a blogger and having 3 posts a week has brought the blog to the front of my mind. Not only did I write many articles, but I’ve started a bunch more and have ideas for even more than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/how-i-blog/</guid>
      <description>Not surprisingly, given my semi random content, I arrive at my posts a few different ways.
1. I better write this down or I’ll never remember it These posts are the result of a rather frustrating night of problem solving. After reading tons of documentation and googling around, reading forums and discussing on IRC I finally got it working. Now I better write it down so I know how to do it next time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Own Private Blogathon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/my-own-private-blogathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/my-own-private-blogathon/</guid>
      <description>Someone once said a goal is a dream until you write it down … in your blog and tell the world about it.
In an effort to focus on blogging a bit more frequently I have decided to start a blogathon beginning today. I will write a post every Monday, Wednesday and Friday for the next four weeks. I think this rate will permit me to continue to keep quality posts, while increasing the frequency and consequently the quantity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured in CIO Magazine!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/featured-in-cio-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/featured-in-cio-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/CIOmag.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Steve Francia in CIO Magazine&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Steve Francia in CIO Magazine &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  I don’t know what could be more shocking that opening this month’s edition of CIO magazine and discovering that my blog, this very blog that you are currently reading is one of two blogs featured this month. I am humbled and honored to be mentioned and included with such great peers. To all my new readers I look forward to connecting with you via Twitter or LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>