<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>spf13-vim on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/spf13-vim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in spf13-vim on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/spf13-vim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I use spf13-vim</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/why-i-use-spf13-vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/why-i-use-spf13-vim/</guid>
      <description>spf13-vim, a completely cross platform distribution of vim plugins and resources for Vim, GVim and MacVim stays true to it&amp;rsquo;s vim roots while adding modern features including a plugin management system, a curated plugin set with customized configuration, advanced autocomplete, tags, support for dozens of languages and much more.
I recently read a thread where the author asked for feedback on whether or not to use spf13-vim. Responses varied greatly with some people loving it to others claiming it was bloated and overkill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spf13-vim 3.0 release and new website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/spf13-vim-3-0-release-and-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/spf13-vim-3-0-release-and-new-website/</guid>
      <description>This post is a bit behind the actual releases, but should be announced here nevertheless. Announcing the 3rd major release of spf13-vim. spf13-vim is a distribution of vim plugins and resources for Vim, GVim and MacVim. It is a completely cross platform distribution that stays true to the feel of vim while providing modern features like a plugin management system, autocomplete, tags and tons more. It grew out of my vim configuration which I put on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>