<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IT on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/IT/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IT on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/IT/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking Vendor References</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/checking-vendor-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/checking-vendor-references/</guid>
      <description>One task that should be part of every IT managers is performing reference checks on potential vendors. A vendor reference check goes beyond the sales pitch to reveal the true nature of a product or company. If you’re not performing reference checks you are susceptible of falling prey to a slick sales pitch with nothing but trouble behind it.
Vendors only provide the customers they are certain will give a glowing endorsement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How RIM handed the mobile market over to Apple</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/how-rim-handed-the-mobile-market-over-to-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/how-rim-handed-the-mobile-market-over-to-apple/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/iphone3.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Image representing iPhone 3G as depicted in Crunchbase&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Image representing iPhone 3G as depicted in Crunchbase &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;  Hint: It has nothing to do with touch screens.
While RIM scrambles to create the next greatest device, or their “iPhone killer” it needs to recognize that it’s no longer about the device. RIM don’t you remember that touchscreens aren’t new.. Palm had them back in the 90′s … before you crushed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire Your Next Consultant Using Twitter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/hire-your-next-consultant-using-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/hire-your-next-consultant-using-twitter/</guid>
      <description>At Portero we had an issue with our network.
I know enough about networking to understand the basics. I actually used to work on the IOS back during the dawn of the internet. Though things have changed since then, the biggest issue is I don’t remember enough to fix network configuration issues on the router level.
Before I took the post at Portero, we had a company we contracted to configure all of our Cisco equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing a Corporate Wiki</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/implementing-a-corporate-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/implementing-a-corporate-wiki/</guid>
      <description>It seems all of a sudden, the two buzz words in the corporate IT world are wiki and blog. Corporate wikis are emerging as cheap, intelligent, flexible systems for shared-document collaboration and content management. Because they are browser based, wikis are quite easy to implement and deploy.
The wiki works well in the corporate world as it solves two problematic areas, the need for internal collaboration and document management.
Collaboration A wiki aims to replace the email, review, reply-to-all, repeat cycle most corporate environments are more than familiar with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>