<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>microsoft on Sometimes we write something:)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:888/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microsoft on Sometimes we write something:)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:888/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development&#39;s Magic Triangle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/software-developments-magic-triangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/software-developments-magic-triangle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/Magic-Triangle-Development.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;Magic Triangle&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  There’s an old adage “Fast, Cheap, Good; Pick Two”. This situation is called a magic triangle. You can have two and only two, if you try for all three you will compromise all three. Fools often try, losing everything.
In the world of software development, another magic triangle exists. You can pick any two of the three, but not all three, so figure out what’s truly important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating interview with Steve Jobs and Bill Gates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/fascinating-interview-with-steve-jobs-and-bill-gates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/fascinating-interview-with-steve-jobs-and-bill-gates/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/Steve_Jobs_and_Bill_Gates.jpg&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  In 2007, All Things Digital held a fascinating interview with both Bill Gates and Steve Jobs.
The interview runs long and is spread out over multiple clips. I’ve only included the first handful here. Watch the rest on youtube.
It’s clear that they have a reasonably good relationship and clearly know each other well. They have a genuine and sincere respect for each other. It’s amazing how firm a grasp both have on the industry as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 7 launch notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:888/post/windows-7-launch-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:888/post/windows-7-launch-notes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;/media/windows-logo.png&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  I was fortunate to be able to attend the Microsoft Launch Developer Preview meeting in NYC. Microsoft is holding these all over the country to prepare IT and developers for the upcoming launch. Overall it was a good meeting and Microsoft is delivering a great product. More importantly they have a really good chance of overcoming the bad taste of vista and emerge as a innovation leader.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>